Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 2. Legislative Files, 1965-2011 TJU.2010.01.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Legislative Assistant Files, 1965-2011; III.
  - Michael Kulis, 1990-2002; 23.
    - Poultry Lab, Biden, 1996 (Box 420, Folder 13)
    - Programs and appropriations, 1994-1996 (Box 420, Folder 14)
    - Programs and appropriations, 1996-1997 (Box 420, Folder 15)
    - Rural economic and community development hearing, 1996 (Box 420, Folder 16)
    - Sugar cap, 1996 (Box 420, Folder 17)
    - Sustainable Agriculture Research and Education (SARE), 1996 (Box 420, Folder 18)
    - USDA Loan, Bill Gindlesperger, 2002 (Box 420, Folder 19)
    - Urban and community forestry program, 1996 (Box 420, Folder 20)
    - Vitaculture grant, 1996 (Box 420, Folder 21)
  - Carey Ann Lackman, 1992-1993; 24.
    Carey Ann Lackman served as legislative assistant (foreign operations, defense, energy, environment), 1993-1994.
    - Business, Brazilian footwear, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 22)
    - Business, Government Relations Council, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 23)
    - Business, Export promotion guidelines, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 24)
    - Business, S. 332, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 25)
    - Business, Timex, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 26)
    - Business, Yardarm, 1992-1993 (Box 420, Folder 27)
    - Constituent mail, British thermal unit tax, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 28)
    - Constituent mail, Farm credit, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 29)
    - Constituent mail, Fay-Penn, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 30)
    - Constituent mail, Furman Bucks, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 31)
    - Constituent mail, Lead tax proposal, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 32)
    - Constituent mail, Market Street building, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 33)
    - Constituent mail, Pennsylvania Small Business United, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 34)
    - Legislative initiatives, 1993 (Box 420, Folder 35)
  - Marybeth LaVerghetta, 1990-2007; 25.
    Marybeth LaVerghetta served as: staff assistant, 2003; legislative correspondent, 2004-2006; and legislative assistant, 2007-2008.
    - Appropriations, Budget Resolution, Drug price negotiations vote (Box 420, Folder 36)
    - Appropriations, Requests, 2004 (Box 420, Folder 37)
    - Appropriations, Requests, 2006 (Box 420, Folder 38)
    - Appropriations, Spreadsheet, 2002 (Box 420, Folder 39)
    - Appropriations, VA/HUD/Independent agencies, 2005 (Box 420, Folder 40)
    - Energy, Air Products and Chemicals, 1999-2003 (Box 420, Folder 41)
    - Energy, Alexander Natural Gas Bills, 2005 (Box 420, Folder 42)
    - Energy, Allegheny Energy, Trans Allegheny Interstate Line (TrAIL), 2007 (Box 420, Folder 43)
    - Energy, Allegheny Energy, Trans Allegheny Interstate Line (TrAIL), 2007 (Box 421, Folder 1)
    - Energy, America Competitiveness Act, 2007 (Box 421, Folder 2)
    - Energy, American Electric Power transmission line, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 1991-2006 (Box 421, Folder 4)
    - Energy, Bioenergy International, 2007 (Box 421, Folder 5)
    - Energy, Blackout 2003, 2003-2004 (Box 421, Folder 6)
    - Energy, China and UNOCAL, 2005 (Box 421, Folder 7)
    - Energy, CITGO/Citizens Energy oil program (Box 421, Folder 8)
    - Energy, Clean coal, 2001 (Box 421, Folder 9)
    - Energy, Clean coal, 2003 (Box 421, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Clean coal, 2003-2004 (Box 421, Folder 11)
    - Energy, Clearfield Biorefinery, 2004-2006 (Box 421, Folder 12)
    - Energy, Clear Skies Initiative, 1990-2002 (Box 421, Folder 13)
    - Energy, Coal research, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 14)
    - Energy, Coke for steel, Section 29 Tax Credits, 2002-2003 (Box 421, Folder 15)
    - Energy, Colonial Pipeline Trail Amendment, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 16)
    - Energy, Columbia Gas (Nisource), 2004-2006 (Box 421, Folder 17)
    - Energy, Comprehensive Environmental Response Compensation & Liability Act, 2006-2007 (Box 421, Folder 18)
    - Energy, Consumer Alliance for Affordable Natural Gas, 2004 (Box 421, Folder 19)
    - Energy, CAFE, 2002 (Box 421, Folder 20)
    - Energy, CAFE, 2005 (Box 421, Folder 21)
    - Energy, Diesel Emissions, 2005-2006 (Box 421, Folder 22)
    - Energy, Energy Bill (109th), 2003-2005 (Box 421, Folder 23)
    - Energy, EPA mercury emissions rule, 2004-2005 (Box 421, Folder 24)
    - Energy, EXECON merger, 2005 (Box 421, Folder 25)
    - Energy, Federal Energy Regulatory Commission (FERC) Standard Market Design, 2003 (Box 421, Folder 26)
    - Energy, Foote mineral superfund site, Whiteland Township, 2004-2007 (Box 421, Folder 27)
    - Energy, Gasoline prices, 2004-2007 (Box 421, Folder 28)
    - Energy, Geothermal, 2003-2004 (Box 421, Folder 29)
    - Energy, Geothermal Heat Pump Consortium, 2002 (Box 421, Folder 30)
    - Energy, GAO study on above-ground storage tanks and SPCC Rule, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 31)
    - Energy, Great Lakes issues, 2001 (Box 421, Folder 32)
    - Energy, Green gas, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 33)
    - Energy, Green Oil Company (Box 421, Folder 34)
    - Energy, Havertown PCP superfund site, 2006 (Box 421, Folder 35)
    - Energy, Hearing statement, 2000 (Box 421, Folder 36)
    - Energy, Hydrogen Fuel Tax Bill, Air Products, 2007 (Box 421, Folder 37)
    - Energy, Ion transport membrane technology, 2004 (Box 421, Folder 38)
    - Energy, Low-Income Home Energy Assistance Program (LIHEAP), 2006 (Box 422, Folder 1)
    - Energy, LIHEAP amendment, 2008 (Box 422, Folder 2)
    - Energy, Mercury rule, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Methyl tertiary butyl ether liability, 2003-2004 (Box 422, Folder 4)
    - Energy, Milford Township Irradiation Facility, 2003-2004 (Box 422, Folder 5)
    - Energy, Mök Industries solar proposal, 2004 (Box 422, Folder 6)
    - Energy, National Coal-to-Liquids Program, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 7)
    - Energy, National Energy Technology Lab, 2004-2007 (Box 422, Folder 8)
    - Energy, National Fuel Gas Company, 2002-2003 (Box 422, Folder 9)
    - Energy, Natural gas, 2003 (Box 422, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Natural gas, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 11)
    - Energy, Natural gas bill, 2006 (Box 422, Folder 12)
    - Energy, Natural gas working group, 2001-2004 (Box 422, Folder 13)
    - Energy, New Hope Crushed Stone and Lime, 2007 (Box 422, Folder 14)
    - Energy, New source review, 2001-2004 (Box 422, Folder 15)
    - Energy, No Oil Producing and Exporting Countries (Cartels Act) materials (Box 422, Folder 16)
    - Energy, Nuclear temperature storage proposal, 2006-2007 (Box 422, Folder 17)
    - Energy, Nuclear waste, 2008 (Box 422, Folder 18)
    - Energy, Oil and gasoline prices industry consolidation, 2006 (Box 422, Folder 19)
    - Energy, Oil Producing and Exporting Countries (OPEC), 2000-2005 (Box 422, Folder 20)
    - Energy, Oil savings, 2003-2005 (Box 422, Folder 21)
    - Energy, Outer continental shelf oil and gas leases, 2006 (Box 422, Folder 22)
    - Energy, Pennsylvania Department of Environmental Protection "EDGE" clean coal proposal, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 23)
    - Energy, Pennsylvania Renewable Portfolio Standard, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 24)
    - Energy, Pennsylvania Rural Electric Association, 2004 (Box 422, Folder 25)
    - Energy, Plextronics Solar Technologies, 2005-2006 (Box 422, Folder 26)
    - Energy, PPL Electric green building, 2003 (Box 422, Folder 27)
    - Energy, Price Anderson Act, 2005 (Box 422, Folder 28)
    - Energy, Renewable fuels, Ethanol, 2003-2005 (Box 422, Folder 29)
    - Energy, Renewable Portfolio Standard, 2003 (Box 423, Folder 1)
    - Energy, Requests, 2003 (Box 423, Folder 2)
    - Energy, Requests, 2005 (Box 423, Folder 3)
    - Energy, Requests (Box 423, Folder 4-5)
    - Energy, Russian uranium shipments, 2003-2004 (Box 423, Folder 6)
    - Energy, Siemens Westinghouse, 2002 (Box 423, Folder 7)
    - Energy, Siemens Westinghouse, Fuel Cells, 2006 (Box 423, Folder 8)
    - Energy, Superfund/ Natural resource damages reform, 2001-2006 (Box 423, Folder 9)
    - Energy, Synthetic Fuel Tax Credit, 2003-2005 (Box 423, Folder 10)
    - Energy, Tax incentives, 2001-2002 (Box 423, Folder 11)
    - Energy, Toxic release inventory rules, 2007 (Box 423, Folder 12)
    - Energy, U.S./Israel energy cooperation, 2004 (Box 423, Folder 13)
    - Energy, Universal aggregates, 2001 (Box 423, Folder 14)
    - Energy, Waste Coal Tax Credit, United Mine Workers Combined Health Benefits Program, 2003-2005 (Box 423, Folder 15)
    - Energy, Water Quality, 2002-2004 (Box 423, Folder 16-17)
    - Energy, Wind Power, 2005 (Box 423, Folder 18)
    - Energy, Yucca Mountain, 2002 (Box 423, Folder 19-21)
    - Environment, 2005 (Box 423, Folder 22)
    - Environment, Brownfields program, 2006 (Box 423, Folder 23)
    - Environment, Chemical security, 2002-2006 (Box 423, Folder 24)
    - Environment, Chesapeake Bay, 2006 (Box 423, Folder 25)
    - Environment, Climate change policy, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 1-2)
    - Environment, Conservation, 2005-2006 (Box 424, Folder 3)
    - Environment, Endangered Species Act, 2006 (Box 424, Folder 4)
    - Environment, Interstate waste, Flow control draft, 1999-2005 (Box 424, Folder 5)
    - Environment, Keystone air pollution, 2000-2005 (Box 424, Folder 6)
    - Environment, McAdoo superfund and blood cancer, 2006-2007 (Box 424, Folder 7)
    - Environment, National Petroleum Reserve, Alaska, Lease sale, 2006 (Box 424, Folder 8)
    - Environment, Off-road small engine emissions, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 9)
    - Environment, Temple University EPA Funding, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 10)
    - Environment, Water amendment, 2006 (Box 424, Folder 11)
    - Homeland Security, 2002-2003 (Box 424, Folder 12)
    - Homeland Security, Agro-Security/Battelle, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 13)
    - Homeland Security, Appropriation requests, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 14)
    - Homeland Security, Community Oriented Policing Services grants, 2003-2004 (Box 424, Folder 15)
    - Homeland Security, Darby Borough/Upper Darby flooding, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 16)
    - Homeland Security, Dektor, Arthur Herring III, 2002-2003 (Box 424, Folder 17)
    - Homeland Security, Dear Colleague letters, 100th Congress, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 18)
    - Homeland Security, Emergency supplemental appropriations, 2005 (Box 424, Folder 19)
    - Homeland Security, Fallen Heroes of 9/11 Act, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 20)
    - Homeland Security, FBI, Ashley Holder Straton, John Steele, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 21)
    - Homeland Security, Federal Bureau of Prisons, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 22)
    - Homeland Security, FEMA, Disaster assistance, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 23)
    - Homeland Security, FEMA, Disaster information, 2001-2004 (Box 424, Folder 24)
    - Homeland Security, FEMA, National Flood Insurance program, 2005 (Box 424, Folder 25)
    - Homeland Security, Fire department grant releases, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 26)
    - Homeland Security, Firefighter grant program, 2001-2002 (Box 424, Folder 27)
    - Homeland Security, Firefighter grant program, 2003 (Box 424, Folder 28)
    - Homeland Security, Firefighter grant program, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 29)
    - Homeland Security, Firefighter grant program, 2005 (Box 424, Folder 30)
    - Homeland Security, Firefighter issues, 2004 (Box 424, Folder 31)
    - Homeland Security, First Responder change requests, 2003 (Box 425, Folder 1)
    - Homeland Security, First Responder initiative, 2001-2004 (Box 425, Folder 2)
    - Homeland Security, Grants, Pennsylvania funding, 2005 (Box 425, Folder 3)
    - Homeland Security, Grants, Pennsylvania funding, 2006 (Box 425, Folder 4)
    - Homeland Security, Hurricane Katrina, 2005-2006 (Box 425, Folder 5)
    - Homeland Security, Juvenile Crime, 2005 (Box 425, Folder 6-7)
    - Homeland Security, Max Energy Savers, 2004 (Box 425, Folder 8)
    - Homeland Security, PATRIOT Act, 2003-2006 (Box 425, Folder 9)
    - Homeland Security, Pennsylvania disaster assistance, 2004 (Box 425, Folder 10)
    - Homeland Security, Pennsylvania floods, 2000-2006 (Box 425, Folder 11)
    - Homeland Security, Port Security Bill, 2002-2003 (Box 425, Folder 12)
    - Homeland Security, RegScan, Ned Ertel, Hazmat Transportation, 2005-2006 (Box 425, Folder 13)
    - Homeland Security, SAP America, 2003 (Box 425, Folder 14)
    - Homeland Security, Small Business Association, Disaster information, 2000-2001 (Box 425, Folder 15)
    - Homeland Security, Symbol Technologies, 2006 (Box 425, Folder 16)
    - Homeland Security, TSA issue, 2006 (Box 425, Folder 17)
    - Homeland Security, Traveler identification, 2006 (Box 425, Folder 18)
    - Homeland Security, Tyco Electronics, 2002 (Box 425, Folder 19)
    - Homeland Security, U.S. VISIT Program, 2006 (Box 425, Folder 20)
    - Homeland Security, Victims of Pan Am 103, 2004 (Box 425, Folder 21)
    - Interior, Abandoned mine reclamation, 2003-2007 (Box 425, Folder 22)
    - Interior, Allegheny National Forrest, 2003-2007 (Box 425, Folder 23)
    - Interior, Allegheny National Forest, 2003-2007 (Box 426, Folder 1)
    - Interior, Appropriations Floor Amendments, 2003 (Box 426, Folder 2)
    - Interior, Arctic National Wildlife Refuge, 2005 (Box 426, Folder 3)
    - Interior, Captain John Smith National Historic Trail, 2004-2007 (Box 426, Folder 4)
    - Interior, Delaware & Lehigh National Heritage Corridor, 2003-2006 (Box 426, Folder 5-6)
    - Interior, Delaware Water Gap National Recreation Area, Route 209, 2005 (Box 426, Folder 7)
    - Interior, Forrest Legacy Program, 2003-2006 (Box 426, Folder 8)
    - Interior, Franklin Institute, 2004-2007 (Box 426, Folder 9)
    - Interior, Gettysburg, 2006-2007 (Box 426, Folder 10)
    - Interior, Hawaiian government reorganization, 2005-2006 (Box 426, Folder 11-12)
    - Interior, Healthy Forest Restoration Act, 2003 (Box 426, Folder 13)
    - Interior, Highlands Stewardship Act, 2002-2006 (Box 426, Folder 14-15)
    - Interior, Logging, 2005 (Box 426, Folder 16)
    - Interior, National Historic Landmarks, 2004-2005 (Box 426, Folder 17)
    - Interior, National Museum of Industrial History, 2002-2003 (Box 426, Folder 18)
    - Interior, National Park Service Director nomination, Mary Bonar, 2006 (Box 426, Folder 19)
    - Interior, Northeastern area state and private forestry, 2005 (Box 426, Folder 20)
    - Interior, Organic Trade Association, 2004 (Box 427, Folder 1)
    - Interior, Priorities, 2003 (Box 427, Folder 2)
    - Interior, Priorities, 2004 (Box 427, Folder 3)
    - Interior, Proposed Cherry Valley National Wildlife Refuge, 2005-2006 (Box 427, Folder 4)
    - Interior, Smart Growth bill, 2005 (Box 427, Folder 5)
    - Interior, Superfund program, 2003 (Box 427, Folder 6)
    - Interior, Take Pride in America (Box 427, Folder 7)
    - Interior, Tongass National Forest, 2004 (Box 427, Folder 8)
    - Interior, U.S. Forest Service relocation to New Mexico (Box 427, Folder 9)
    - Interior, Valley Forge Citizens for Deer Control, 2000-2004 (Box 427, Folder 10)
  - Malcolm Lee, 1980-1985; 26.
    Malcolm Lee served as legislative correspondent, 1983-1984.
    - Compilation of reports and statements, 1980s (Box 427, Folder 11)
    - Counterterrorism, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 12)
    - Daybook, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 13)
    - Foreign issues, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 14)
    - Foreign trips, 1981-1983 (Box 427, Folder 15)
    - Nuclear disarmament constituent mail, 1983 (Box 427, Folder 16)
    - Office manual, 1983 (Box 427, Folder 17-18)
    - Pennsylvania trips, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 19-20)
    - Reagan inauguration, 1985 (Box 427, Folder 21)
    - Telephone messages, 1985 (Box 427, Folder 22)
    - Year-end summary, 1983 (Box 427, Folder 23)
    - Year-end summary, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 24)
  - Brian Lindberg, 1980-1985; 27.
    Brian Lindberg served as legislative assistant, 1984-1985.
    - Allegheny Labor Project, 1983 (Box 427, Folder 25)
    - American Federation of Government Employees, 1985 (Box 427, Folder 26)
    - AFL-CIO News, 1984 (Box 427, Folder 27)
    - Appalachian Trail, 1982-1983 (Box 427, Folder 28)
    - Bills and reports, 1982 (Box 427, Folder 29)
    - Bills and reports, 1982 (Box 428, Folder 1)
    - Bills and reports (Box 428, Folder 2-4)
    - Cable amendment, 1982 (Box 428, Folder 5)
    - Carnegie Mellon University, 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 6)
    - Coal gasification, 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 7)
    - Coal leasing, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 8)
    - Community Development Block Grant, 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 9)
    - Container Corporation, 1982 (Box 428, Folder 10)
    - Defense appropriations, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 11)
    - District Heating and Cooling, 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 12)
    - Energy research, Wood products, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 13)
    - Enterprise Zone Initiative, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 14)
    - Environment, 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 15-16)
    - Farmers Home Administration, 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 17)
    - FCC, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 18)
    - Federal-State Joint Telecommunications Board, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 19)
    - Federal Trade Commission (FTC), 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 20)
    - Fish and wildlife, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 21)
    - Food and nutrition programs, 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 22)
    - Forestry, undated (Box 428, Folder 23)
    - Gypsy moths, 1983-1984 (Box 428, Folder 24)
    - Housing modernization, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 25)
    - Job training, 1981-1982 (Box 428, Folder 26)
    - Judicial nominations, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 27)
    - Juvenile Justice, 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 28)
    - Labor, 1982-1985 (Box 428, Folder 29)
    - Labor, Health and Human Services, and Education appropriations, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 30)
    - Logging, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous, 1983-1984 (Box 428, Folder 32)
    - Moratorium on flat telephone rates, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 33)
    - National Park Service, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 34)
    - Native Americans, 1983-1984 (Box 428, Folder 35)
    - OSHA, 1982 (Box 428, Folder 36)
    - Penn State, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 37)
    - Possible floor amendments, 1983-1984 (Box 428, Folder 38)
    - Potatoes, 1982-1983 (Box 428, Folder 39)
    - Prisons and health care, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 40)
    - Project Democracy, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 41)
    - Purged coal, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 42)
    - Radioactive waste, 1983 (Box 428, Folder 43)
    - Refugees and prisons, 1981-1983 (Box 428, Folder 44)
    - Rural electrification, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 1)
    - Sludge, 1980-1983 (Box 429, Folder 2)
    - Soil conservation, 1982-1983 (Box 429, Folder 3)
    - Solar Bank, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 4)
    - Strategic Petroleum Reserve, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 5)
    - Temporary Natural Gas Market Correction Act, 1982 (Box 429, Folder 6)
    - Trade Adjustment Assistance, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 7)
    - Urban gardening, 1981-1982 (Box 429, Folder 8)
    - Urban parks, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 9)
    - Veterans, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 10)
    - Washington Public Power Supply System, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 11)
    - Water Resources Development Act, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 12)
    - Westinghouse, 1983 (Box 429, Folder 13)
    - Whale and dolphin hunting, 1982-1983 (Box 429, Folder 14)
    - Wish lists, 1981-1982 (Box 429, Folder 15)
    - Wish lists, 1982-1983 (Box 429, Folder 16)
  - Doug Loon, 1985-1995; 28.
    Doug Loon served as: legislative correspondent, 1988; legislative assistant (agriculture, governmental affairs, oversight, transportation), 1989; and legislative director, 1991-1995.
    - Budget, 1994-1995 (Box 429, Folder 17-18)
    - Major farm bills, 1985-1990 (Box 429, Folder 19)
    - Trip files, 1990-1991 (Box 429, Folder 20)
  - Eugene "Skip" Maupai, 1995-1998; 29.
    Eugene "Skip" Maupai served as legislative correspondent, 1998.
    - Boxing, 1997 (Box 429, Folder 21)
    - Boys Nation/American Legion, 1997 (Box 429, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of Alcohol, Tobacco, Firearms and Explosives, 1996 (Box 429, Folder 23)
    - Congressional records, 1997-1998 (Box 429, Folder 24)
    - Constituent mail, 1995-1997 (Box 429, Folder 25)
    - Co-sponsored resolutions, 1997-1998 (Box 429, Folder 26)
    - Deegan Law, 1997 (Box 429, Folder 27)
    - Habeas corpus limitation, 1997 (Box 429, Folder 28)
    - Judiciary Committee, 1997-1998 (Box 429, Folder 29)
    - Judiciary letters, 1997-1998 (Box 429, Folder 30)
    - Raymark Corporation, 1997 (Box 429, Folder 31)
  - Dobie McArthur, 1992-2001; 30.
    Dobie McArthur served as legislative director, 1999-2001.
    - Abortion issue and GOP platform, 1992-1995 (Box 429, Folder 32-33)
    - Army Corps of Engineers dredging and flood control projects, 1992-1999 (Box 429, Folder 34-36)
    - Army Corps of Engineers dredging and flood control projects, 1992-1999 (Box 430, Folder 1)
    - Balanced Budget Reconciliation Act, 1995 (Box 430, Folder 2)
    - Bill files, 105th Congress, 1997 (Box 430, Folder 3)
    - Colonel Ernest C. Beinhart and George C. Marshall European Center for Security Studies investigation, 1999 (Box 430, Folder 4-5)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Algeria, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 6)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Angola, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 7)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Democratic Republic of Congo, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 8)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Ghana, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 9)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Mali, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 10)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Portugal, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 11)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Senegal, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 12)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, South Africa, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 13)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Spain, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 14)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Tunisia, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 15)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Uganda, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 16)
    - CODEL Shelby visit, Zambia, 2000 (Box 430, Folder 17)
    - Cox Report, Loral and Hughes information, 1999 (Box 430, Folder 18-19)
    - Cox Report, Responses, 1999-2000 (Box 430, Folder 20-21)
    - Democratic National Committee/Chinese government contribution investigation newsclips, 1995-1996 (Box 430, Folder 22)
    - Department of Energy documents, 1999 (Box 430, Folder 23)
    - Department of Justice Oversight (DOJO), Memos, 1997-1999 (Box 431, Folder 1)
    - DOJO, Memos, 2000 (Box 431, Folder 2-3)
    - DOJO, Memos, 2001 (Box 431, Folder 4)
    - DOJO, Notes, 1999-2001 (Box 431, Folder 5-8)
    - DOJO, Senate Judiciary Committee, 1999-2000 (Box 431, Folder 9)
    - DOJO, Waco federal raid and federal law enforcement activities, 1996 (Box 431, Folder 10)
    - Foreign Intelligence Surveillance Act Amendment, 2000 (Box 431, Folder 11-13)
    - IRS audit initiative, 1995 (Box 431, Folder 14)
    - Judiciary hearings, 2000 (Box 431, Folder 15)
    - Peter Hoong-Yee Lee, Chinese espionage investigation, 1999 (Box 431, Folder 16)
    - Peter Hoong-Yee Lee, Espionage investigation office memos, 1999-2000 (Box 432, Folder 1-2)
    - Wen Ho Lee, 1999-2000 (Box 432, Folder 3)
    - Wen Ho Lee, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 4-5)
    - Wen Ho Lee, Department of Energy psychophysiological detection of deception report, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 6)
    - Wen Ho Lee, Hearing briefing book, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 7-8)
    - Wen Ho Lee, Transcript of proceedings, August, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 9-12)
    - Wen Ho Lee, Transcript of Proceedings, September-December, 2000 (Box 432, Folder 13-16)
    - Legislative Reorganization Act, 1994 (Box 433, Folder 1)
    - Philadelphia Department of Customs Management Center, 1994-1995 (Box 433, Folder 2)
    - Political advocacy and federal grant restrictions, 1995 (Box 433, Folder 3-4)
    - Reading and General Services Administration dispute, 1991-1994 (Box 433, Folder 5)
    - Yah Lin Trie, 2000 (Box 433, Folder 6)
    - Weapons of Mass Destruction Commission and Automated Export System, 1999 (Box 433, Folder 7-9)
    - White House E-Mail and Automated Records Management System (ARMS) issue, 2000 (Box 433, Folder 10-11)
  - Debbie McIlroy, 1985-1986; 31.
    Debbie McIlroy worked in Senator Specter's office, with materials dated 1985-1986.
    - Conrail, 1985 (Box 433, Folder 12-16)
    - Eminent domain, 1986 (Box 434, Folder 1)